Someone passed on a message,
أرسل أحدهم رسالة
asking me to take good care of Xu Wenguo.
أن أعتني بشو ون قوه
You made this gun
لقد صنعت هذا المسدس
and killed Li Chao.
وقتلت لي تشاو
I didn't shoot at that time.
لم أطلق النار
We didn't kill anyone.
‫لم نقتل أحد‬
I really didn't shoot!
‫لم أقم بفتحه حقا‬
I didn't!
لم أفتحه
I heard a bang.
سمعت صوت بنغ
Go to hell!
الموت
Officer Du,
أيها الضابط دو
please believe us.
ثق بنا
Neither of us killed anyone.
لم نقتل أحد
Everybody, get moving!
تحركوا
You only have 15 minutes.
لدينا 15 دقيقة فقط
Sir.
سيدي
Miss, are you done?
أيها الرفيق هل انتهيت
I have something urgent.
لدي أمر طارئ
Mine is more urgent.
أنا في عجلة من أمري
Sir, can I make another call?
سيدي هل يمكنني الاتصال مرة أخرى
It didn't go through just now.
لا
Thanks.
شكرا
Hello?
ألو
Hello, hi.
مرحبا
I'm looking for Du Xiangdong.
أبحث عن دو شيانغ دونغ
Alright, no problem.
حسنا لا مشكلة
I'll have him call you back when he returns.
سأجعله يرد إليك عندما يعود
Okay.
حسنا
Hold on a minute.
انتظر
Du, it's for you.
شياو دو
Who is it?
من
The one who left a stamp of love for you.
‫تلك التي رسمت لك علامة الحب‬
The beauty from the meat processing plant.
شي شي من مصنع اللحم
Just say I'm not around.
أخبرهم أنني لست هنا
Wait...
لا
She's been calling you all afternoon.
لقد اتصلت بك طوال الظهر
Just answer it.
أجب
Tell her I'm dead.
قل إنني ميت
How am I supposed to make that up?
كيف أصنع هذا؟
Dead?
مات
Miss,
أيها الرفيق
Du
شياو دو
has been feeling under the weather lately.
إنه ليس على ما يرام مؤخرًا
What?
ماذا حدث؟
What's wrong with him?
ما الخطب؟
What's wrong?
هل أنت بخير؟
He just...
إنه
He's been stressed out lately.
إنه تحت ضغط كبير مؤخرًا
And with his poor health,
جسده ضعيف جدا
he ended up
مما أدى إلى
having a hemorrhoid flare-up.
أصيب ببشرة
Hemorrhoid?
البشرة
You wouldn't believe it.
أنت لا تعرف
It's bleeding like crazy.
إنه دمه ينزف
Literally a terrible sight.
‫بائس جدا‬
That poor thing.
لقد ارتكبت الكثير من الجرائم
Can I go check in on him?
هل يمكنني زيارته؟
No, please don't!
لا تأتي لرؤيته
Why can't I visit him?
لماذا لا يمكنني زيارته؟
Because...
لأن
Think about it.
فكري بالأمر
You're a lady.
زميلتك
It's improper for you
الجزء الخاص به
to check that part of his body.
غير مريح
Well...
إذن
We'll take good care of him for you.
سنساعدك في الاعتناء به
Don't worry.
لا تقلق
Oh, okay.
حسنا حسنا
Thank you then.
شكرا لكم
take care of him.
أرجو منكم أن تعتنوا به من أجلي
Yes, sure.
نعم نعم نعم
Please tell him
أخبريه
Liu Fenfang was calling him, okay?
أن ليو فنفانغ اتصلت به
Okay, alright.
نعم نعم نعم نعم
No problem.
لا مشكلة
Thank you.
شكرا
Okay, okay.
حسنا حسنا
Bye-bye.
مع السلامة
Goodbye, goodbye.
مع السلامة مع السلامة
Hemorrhoid flare-up? Seriously?
أنت مصاب ببشرة فقط
Don't you think
أنا لست في عجلة من أمري
I'm quick-witted?
أليس كذلك
Why are you not back home?
لماذا لم تعودي للمنزل
I'm on duty today.
اليوم في الخدمة
Is it your shift today?
هل أنت في الخدمة اليوم
Du,
شياو دو
since you're here,
بما أنك هنا
can you do me a favor
يمكنك أن تقدم أسلوبك
and cover my shift today?
اليوم
Tomorrow I'll ask my wife to make you
سأطلب من زوجتك
some delicious food
أن تحضر لك بعض الطعام اللذيذ
and bring it over for you.
وأحضره لك
Thank you!
شكرا
What are you doing?
ماذا تقصد
What do you mean?
ماذا تعني
Why do you
امتص أنفك دائما
keep sniffling?
ماذا تعني؟
I have rhinitis.
لدي التهاب الأنف
My nose is stuffed up.
أنفي لا يعمل
What are you trying to say?
ماذا تقصد؟
Nothing, never mind.
لا شيء
You're so funny.
أنت مضحك
Du Xiangdong.
دو شيانغ دونغ
Well, um...
ماذا
Have a tangerine.
تناولي البرتقال
It's freshly picked from the mountain.
قطفتها من الجبل للتو
Can you go wash your hands first?
لماذا لا تغسل يدك
I just washed them after work.
لقد غسلتها بعد العمل
They're not dirty.
لا
How old are you again?
كم عمرك
Do you mind dating someone older than you?
هل تمانع أن تكون أكبر منك
Here you are.
كلي البرتقال
I have a question for you.
أسألك سؤالا
Why do you keep ignoring my calls
لماذا لا تجيب على هاتفي
and messages?
تجاهلني
I'm sick.
أنا مريضة
But it's not like you have hemorrhoids on your hands!
يدك ليست مصابة بالبشرة
You already have a boyfriend.
لديك حبيب
Why are you still contacting me?
لماذا تتصل بي
Who do you mean?
‫من
Zhang Xiangyang?
‫تشانغ شيانغ يانغ
I never said yes to him.
.لم أعدك قط
Remember his hand on your leg? And you still deny it?
لقد وضعت يدك على ساقك لكنك لا تعترف
Say that again.
قل ذلك مرة أخرى
Are you jealous?
هل تغار؟
So petty.
بخيل
Open your mouth.
افتح فمك
I don't want it. You eat it.
لا آكل أنت تأكل
Try one!
تناولي واحدة
I'll go get you a glass of water.
سأحضر لك كوبا من الماء
Do you have coffee?
هل لديك القهوة
No.
لا
Is malted milk okay?
‫هل هذا جيد؟‬
Okay.
‫حسنا‬
Your place
هذا المكان
is too far from downtown.
بعيد جدا عن المدينة
We can't live here after we get married.
لا يمكنك العيش هنا بعد الزواج
Or it would be a pain to go watch a play.
وإلا سيكون من غير المناسب مشاهدة المسرحية
And this bed of yours...
وهذا السرير
You've thrown your clothes all over it.
هل رميت هذه الملابس بشكل عشوائي
Have you washed them?
هل غسلت أم لا
Yep.
لقد غسلتها
You really need someone
لا يوجد أحد هنا
to take care of you,
حقا لا يمكن
you know?
أقول لك
Alright, stop fussing around.
حسنًا، توقف عن العمل
It's okay.
لا بأس
I'll wrap it up in a minute.
سينتهي قريبا
I put in two spoonfuls for you.
وضعت لك thìتين
I usually only have one spoonful.
أنا عادة أشرب thìة واحدة
What's wrong?
ما الخطب؟
You're still living here!
هل يوجد شخص يعيش هنا؟
You're also keeping mice?
هل تربيت الفأر
Is it clean water?
هل الماء نظيف
It's fine for washing.
ممكن
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Put that down!
اتركه بسرعة
Why did you pick it up?
لا تزال تأخذها
You haven't cleaned your place for a long time, huh?
لقد مر وقت طويل على تنظيف النظافة
Where's the kitchen?
أين المطبخ؟
I'll go stew the pork trotters for you.
سأحضر لك 족 الخنزير
Are you Ms. Cui,
أنت تسوي لي تشن
Cui Lizhen?
العمة تسوي
I'm from the city's No.1 Detention Center.
أنا من مركز الاعتقال الأول في المدينة
Yao Binbin is currently kept there.
ياو بين بين في مكاننا الآن
I'm a prison guard at that center.
أنا مدرب هناك
Excuse me.
افسحوا الطريق
Just one more day in bed,
استلقي ليوم آخر
and you can be discharged tomorrow.
يمكنك الخروج من المستشفى غدًا
Before you leave, remember
تذكر قبل أن تغادر
to have the factory staff come and settle the bill.
‫اطلب من شخص من المصنع دفع الحساب‬
How are my two sons doing?
هل أبني بخير
Please don't wrongly accuse them.
لا يمكن أن يظلمهم
That gun is fake.
هذا المسدس مزيف
It's just a toy gun.
إنه مسدس لعبة
It can't be fired.
لا يمكن إطلاق النار
You've seen that gun too?
لقد رأيت ذلك المسدس
Two months ago,
قبل شهرين
when I was cleaning under the bed,
كنت أنظف السرير
I pulled out a cardboard box,
‫بمجرد سحب صندوق ورق
and that gun dropped to the floor.
سقط المسدس على الأرض
Mom,
أمي
this gun doesn't work anymore.
لا يمكن إطلاق هذا المسدس الآن
Let me show you.
دعني أريك
It can't be fired.
هل أطلق النار؟
He pulled the trigger several times,
اسحب المسدس
but it just didn't fire.
لا يمكن أن نطلق النار
Time for lunch.
حان وقت الطعام
Wenguo wouldn't lie.
لن تكذب ون قوه
What about her?
هذا السرير
She didn't order it.
لم تحجز
The hospital food is a bit expensive.
الطعام في المستشفى غالي بعض الشيء
My neighbor brought me food.
لقد أرسلها الجيران لي
I brought you the pork trotter soup.
أحضرت لك حساء الأقدام
Thank you.
شكرا
That neighbor of yours,
جارتك
Chen Su'e,
تشين سو يا
doesn't she bring you food every day?
ألم ترسل لك الطعام كل يوم؟
Why hasn't she come with it today?
لماذا لم تأتي اليوم
She hasn't shown up the past two days.
لم تأت هذه الأيام
Maybe she's been busy with something.
ربما حدث شيء ما
She hasn't been here for two days?
لم تأت منذ يومين
Ms. Cui is still waiting for me to bring her food.
العمة تسوي تنتظرني لتوصيل الطعام
Can I go prepare it?
هل يمكنني أن أستعد
Come on, take it
هيا، بينما تكون دافئة
while it's still warm.
اشرب بسرعة
Chen Su'e didn't come last night?
ألم يأت تشين سو يا الليلة الماضية؟
No, she didn't.
لا
Cheese!
الباذنجان
Dear neighbors,
أيها الجيران
my father is ill,
الأب العجوز مريض
so I'm back home to take care of him.
سأعود إلى المنزل لأعتني به
I'll be back soon.
سأعود قريباً
By Chen Su'e.
تشين سو يا
Anybody home?
هل من أحد هنا؟
Catch the thief!
أمسكوا بالسرقة
Hurry up!
بسرعة بسرعة
Come on! Don't let him escape!
بسرعة بسرعة لا تدعه يهرب
Catch him!
أمسكوا به
Don't move!
لا تتحرك
Get down! Get down!
انبطحوا
Don't move! Get down!
لا تتحركوا
I'm a cop! Cop!
الشرطة الشرطة
Get down! Now! Get down!
‫انبطحوا انبطحوا
Head, we caught a thief.
‫أيها الرئيس لقد قبضنا على اللص
Officer Du?
‫الضابط دو
Put them down!
اتركه
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل
Officer Du, this...
أيها الضابط دو
This is a misunderstanding.
لقد أسأت الفهم
I told you
لقد أخبرتك المرة السابقة
to inform us
قبل أن تأتي
before you come.
قبل مجيئك
If you did,
إذًا
there wouldn't be such a misunderstanding!
لن يكون هناك سوء فهم
Did any of you hit him?
هل قتلتم؟
No.
لا لا
Tell the truth!
بصراحة
Did you hit him?
هل لديك
No, I didn't.
لا لا
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
Should I say thank you?
يجب أن أشكرك حقا
You've really made our center
هذه المرة
famous this time.
في مكتبنا
I wonder if I stand a chance to see you
لا أعرف قبل تقاعدي
completely disgrace
قبل تقاعدي
our center before I retire.
وأحرج سمعتنا
Chief,
رئيس
Du meant well.
شياو دو طيب القلب
I'll talk to him later.
سأتحدث عنه بعد قليل
And you too, Wu!
‫لاو وو لم يقل عنك أليس كذلك
You keep pretending everything's okay!
كل يوم
I told you to watch over him!
طلبت منك أن تراقبه
What have you done?
ماذا فعلت؟
Yes,
نعم
I failed to fulfill my duty.
لم أنجز عملي بشكل جيد
Chief,
أيها المدير
I think there's something fishy about
أعتقد أن شو ون قوه و ياو بين بين
the case of Xu Wenguo and Yao Binbin.
هناك مشكلة في هذه القضية
What's wrong with it?
ما المشكلة
You think
هل تعتقد
you're a criminal police officer?
أنت شرطي
Just focus on your own job properly!
‫قم بعملك‬
How could you have the nerve to run around?
كيف تجرؤين على الهرب
You went to the hospital
إلى المستشفى
to meet Cui Lizhen
لزيارة تسوي لي تشن
and sneaked into one's house
ثم ذهبت إلى منزله
to look for evidence.
للبحث عن الأدلة سرا
And what happened?
والنتيجة
You got caught red-handed.
تم القبض عليه
Isn't that embarrassing?
هل هذا محرج؟
What's wrong with you?
هل أنت مجنون؟
You're right, Chief.
الرئيس على حق
Listen, Du Xiangdong.
دعني أخبرك دو شيانغ دونغ
A horse can run wild on the grasslands.
يمكن الحصان أن يتجول في المراعي
But here under my command,
لكن في مكاني
on this chessboard, the Horse
على لوحة الشطرنج
must move accordingly in a chess game.
يجب أن نمشي الشمس
Why?
لماذا؟
Because there are rules
لأن هناك قواعد
and disciplines.
هناك نظام
Rules and disci...
القواعد والقوانين
I didn't see it.
لم أره لم أره
That doesn't count.
لا لا
I'll undo that move.
تندم خطوة بخطوة تندم خطوة بخطوة
I...
أنا
I'm going with this move.
سأذهب إلى هنا
Here's my heads-up for you.
دعني أذكرك
That police uniform you're wearing
هذه الزي الشرطي
is like the iron horseshoe nailed to your hoof,
‫هي الأقدام الحديدية التي وضعتها لك‬
the bridle on your head,
‫قفص‬
and the reins holding you tight.
حبل
I don't care about your thoughts,
لا يهمني إذا كنت في قلبك
but here, you must follow the rules.
يجب أن تغادر هنا
Chief, he understands now.
سيدي، لقد علم ذلك
You got it, right?
فهمت
Alright.
حسنًا
Submit a self-criticism report and take a demerit.
اكتب المراجعة
Agreed.
منافس
I strongly suggest that
أقترح بشدة
at the staff meeting,
في الاجتماع
Du Xiangdong should
دع الرفيق دو شيانغ دونغ
do a thorough self-criticism.
اكتب تقريرًا عميقًا
It must be a complete process.
يجب أن يكون واحد
Did you hear that?
هل سمعت؟
Chief,
سيدي
we can't close this case so easily like this.
إذا تم الحكم على هذه القضية
It's about two lives!
ستكون حياتان
Xu Wenguo and Yao Binbin
شو ون قوه و ياو بين بين
are only in their twenties.
عمرهما أكثر من عشرين سنة
If you wrongly execute them,
إذا قتلت الشخص الخطأ
it's not a chess game where you can
هذا ليس لعب الشطرنج
retract a move!
هل ستندم؟
That stubborn brat.
هذا الطفل الأحمق
Chief,
سيدي
I...
أنا أنا
Du! Du!
شياو دو شياو دو
Checkmate.
أيها الجنرال
I'm done! No more games!
لا
You need a haircut now.
حان وقت قص شعرك
Chief,
سيدي
this is a wig.
شعري مستعار
I've been losing a lot of hair recently.
تسقط شعري بشكل شرس مؤخرًا
Then you should get another one!
يجب أن تغيري
This one doesn't meet regulations at all.
هذا غير مناسب على الإطلاق
Yes, sir.
نعم
None of them gives me peace of mind.
لا يوجد أحد يقلق
Officer Du.
أيها القائد دو
Wu.
وو
You're on night duty today, right?
‫هل أنتِ في الدوام الليلي اليوم‬
Yes.
نعم
I'll take your shift.
أنا أستحق ذلك من أجلك
Why are you taking my shift?
ما العمل الذي تنوب عني؟
You helped my daughter
لقد ساعدت
a lot last time.
في المرة السابقة
I haven't even thanked you properly.
لم أشكرك
Don't bother taking my shift.
لا داعي لأن تستحقني
I'd like to
أريد أن
have a good talk with Xu Wenguo and Yao Binbin tonight.
أن أتحدث مع شو ون قوه و ياو بين بين
Talking to them
تحدث معهم
is within the rules.
هذا مناسب للقوانين
But it's your night shift again tomorrow.
لكن غدا سيكون نومك الليلي
Can your health handle it?
هل يمكنك تحمل ذلك؟
I can't cover your shift tomorrow.
لا يمكنني مساعدتك غدا
My daughter is on holiday tomorrow.
حفيدك في عطلة غدًا
I want to spend more time with her.
أريد البقاء معها
As you should.
فلتبقي مع ابنتك
I'll take all the night shifts for a while.
‫هذه الفترة من العمل الليلي لي‬
You're so nice, bro.
صادق يا أخي
Thanks!
شكرا
They're accomplices!
هما شريكان
You can't talk to them both at once!
لا يمكنك التحدث معه
I know.
فهمت
And don't do anything recklessly.
لا تتصرف بتهور
Officer Du,
أيها القائد دو
I didn't kill anyone.
لم أقتل أحد
I'm telling you the truth.
أقول لك الحقيقة
That gun is fake.
هذا المسدس مزيف
It couldn't kill anyone.
‫لا يمكن أن يقتل أحد على الإطلاق
Don't fool me with the same trick
‫لا تخدعني
you used on Zhang Xiangyang.
‫خدعتني
Do you know
لماذا جئت إلى هنا
why I'm here?
هل تعرف ذلك؟
Am I here to help you or harm you?
هل سأساعدك أم أؤذيك
I went to meet him
كنت أبحث عنه
just to scare him a bit
كنت أحاول إخافته
and beat him up.
أضربه
But he was not scared.
لكنه لا يخاف فقط
He even laughed at me and said I...
لماذا تضحك علي؟
I didn't dare to fire the gun.
لا أجرؤ على إطلاق النار
Then, in a fit of rage,
ثم غضبت
I pulled the trigger.
‫فأمسكت بندقية
But Officer Du,
لكن أيها المدير دو
I really didn't know
أنا حقا لا أعرف
why that gun could fire.
لماذا يمكن أن يرن البندقية
So,
لذلك
you did shoot Li Chao.
لقد أطلقت النار على لي تشاو
Yes.
نعم
Officer Du,
أيها المدير دو
what do you mean by that?
ماذا تعني؟
The gun you made
الشخص الذي قتل لي تشاو
was what killed Li Chao.
هو المسدس الذي صنعته
That gun didn't even have a firing pin.
‫لم يصطدم المسدس على الإطلاق
I took out the firing pin myself!
لقد أخرجت الحقنة بنفسي
It really couldn't fire!
لا يمكن فتحها على الإطلاق
Then tell me
أخبرني
when you first realized that
متى اكتشفت
this gun couldn't work.
أن هذا المسدس لا يصرخ
When I saved my brother at the pool hall.
عندما أنقذت أخي في الملعب
I'll shoot whoever dares to
من يجرؤ على لمس أخي؟
hurt my brother!
سأقتل من
My brother tried to fire a shot then,
‫كان أخي يحمل طلقة النار
but the gun didn't go off.
لم يرن المسدس.
Later, I asked my brother what happened.
ثم سألت أخي ماذا حدث
He said he had removed the firing pin.
قال أنه أخذ الحقنة
From that day on, I knew
عرفت منذ ذلك اليوم
this gun was just for show.
‫أن هذا المسدس مزيف
It couldn't fire at all.
لا يمكن إطلاق النار على الإطلاق
So,
لذلك
you made a new firing pin and put it back in.
قمت بصنع الحقنة مرة أخرى
Then you shot and killed Li Chao.
أطلق النار على لي تشاو
I would never harm my younger brother!
لا يمكنني أن أؤذي أخي
To be honest with you,
أقول لك الحقيقة
when my brother and I made that gun,
إن المسدس الذي صنعته أنا وأخي
we were indeed aiming to kill Li Chao!
من أجل لي تشاو
Then Ms. Cui found out.
ثم عرفت العمة تسوي
She came to me in tears,
جاءت إلي بكاء
asking us not to do anything crazy.
‫وقالت لا تدعنا نفعل أشياء غبية‬
I promised Ms. Cui,
لقد وعدت العمة تسوي
so I took out the firing pin from the gun
‫سأخرج الحقنة في البندقية‬
and hid it.
لقد أخفيت
Xu Wenguo,
شو ون قوه
you didn't behave yourself.
أنت غير صادق
If you really didn't want to use this gun,
إن كنتم لا تريدون استخدام هذا المسدس
you should have thrown away the firing pin.
يجب أن تخلص من الحقنة
Why did you hide it?
لماذا تخفيه
To commit crimes in the future?
استمر في ارتكاب الجريمة في المستقبل
To take revenge?
انتقام المجتمع
Who else knows that
من يعرف
you two made a gun?
من يعرف أيضا
No one else knows.
لا أحد يعرف
Think carefully.
فكر مرة أخرى
Does your mother know?
هل والدتك تعرف؟
No, she doesn't.
لا تعرف
That gun is fake.
أن المسدس مزيف
It's just a toy gun.
إنه مسدس لعبة
You're lying again.
أنت تكذب مرة أخرى
Your mother admitted that
اعترفت والدتك بنفسها
she once saw that gun.
أنها رأت ذلك المسدس
You made this gun
لقد صنعت هذا المسدس
and killed Li Chao.
وقتلت لي تشاو
Li Chao was a bastard.
لي تشاو وحش
I had put up with him for over a decade!
لقد تحملته لأكثر من عشر سنوات
Trust me! It's not a real gun.
هل تصدق أن مسدسي حقيقي أم مزيف
It couldn't fire!
لا يمكن إطلاق النار
Binbin fired the gun
أطلق "بين بين"
and killed Li Chao.
لقد قتلت لي تشاو
Ms. Cui is still waiting for my food.
الأخت تسوي تنتظرني لأطبخ
Maybe she's been busy with something. She hasn't shown up.
ربما حدث شيء ما ولم تأت
Someone passed on a message,
أرسل أحدهم رسالة
asking me to take good care of Xu Wenguo.
أن أعتني بشو ون قوه
I promised Ms. Cui,
لقد وعدت العمة تسوي
so I took out the firing pin from the gun
‫سأخرج الحقنة في البندقية‬
and hid it.
لقد أخفيت
Where did you hide it?
أين أخفيت؟
In my kitchen.
المطبخ.
Hello, Mr. Liu.
‫مرحبا أيها الرئيس ليو‬
The police have entered the factory!
‫دخلت الشرطة المصنع‬
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل
Step back!
تراجعوا
Officer Zhang.
الضابط تشانغ
It's me.
إنه أنا
Take a close look.
انظر بوضوح
The search warrant.
بطاقة البحث
Please cooperate with our work.
أرجو أن تتعاون معنا
Alright, alright.
نعم نعم نعم
And specific location?
الموقع المحدد
Inside the hemp rope used for hanging cured meat.
في الحبل المقلي
Xu Wenguo,
شو ون قوه
That gun went off on the day of the incident.
صوت البندقية في يوم الحادث
How do you explain that?
‫كيف تفسر ذلك
You're right.
أنت على حق
Maybe someone put the firing pin back in.
قد يكون هناك شخص وضع الحقنة إلى المنزل
Was it you?
أنت
Or Yao Binbin?
أو ياو بين بين
Officer Zhang.
الضابط تشانغ
The investigation is over?
انتهى التحقيق
We've got the pin.
لقد أخذت الأشياء
Let's talk about it tomorrow.
لنتحدث غدا
Any fingerprints on it?
‫هل يوجد بصمات في الأعلى
We've extracted one fingerprint.
استخراج بصمات
It belongs to Xu Wenguo.
شو ون قوه
Seems like Xu Wenguo didn't lie.
يبدو أن شو ون قوه لم يكذب
He put the firing pin in.
هو من وضع الحقنة
Does it match this gun?
هل يناسب هذا المسدس؟
It fits into the gun,
نعم.
not perfectly though.
لكن خفيف قليلا
I have a question.
لدي سؤال
Why are there no fingerprints
لماذا لا يوجد بصمات الأصابع
on the firing pin of this gun?
بصمات الأصابع؟
Long-term use causes wear and tear.
‫يستخدم التعذيب لفترة طويلة‬
No fingerprints left for sure.
لا توجد بصمات
But I think these two sets of firing pins
لكن أعتقد أن هذين المجموعتين
look completely different.
مختلفة تمامًا
I don't understand
لا أفهم
why parts made by the same person
لماذا يوجد فرق كبير
can be so different.
يمكن أن يكون هناك فرق كبير
Lady, you think this is
أختي هل تعتقدين أن هذا
a standard-issue gun
سلاح نظيف
made to exactly the same specs?
كل سلاح متشابه
This is a homemade gun.
هذا مسدس مصنوع
The parts
الأجزاء
were machined one by one.
تخرج سيارة واحدة تلو الأخرى
Let me ask you.
أسألك
Can you draw two
هل يمكنك الرسم
identical paintings?
في نفس الوقت؟
Look.
انظر إلى هذا
The pointed one found at Yao Binbin's house.
‫تم العثور على رأس رقيق في منزل ياو بين بين‬
The round one of this gun.
‫رأس مستدير في هذا المسدس‬
Everyone, get out of the rooms!
غادر الجميع الغرفة
Run!
اذهب بسرعة
Earthquake! Earthquake!
زلزال زلزال
Everyone, get out!
غادروا الغرفة
Help!
النجدة
Come on, hurry!
هيا بسرعة بسرعة
Quickly bring out the rest of them!
أخرجوا الباقي
Officers, do head counts by cells!
‫كل تعليمات قم بالتسجيل وفقًا للمراقبة‬
Now, roll call!
سنبدأ بالتسجيل الآن
-Zhao Shugang! -Here!
تشاو شو قانغ حاضر
-Zhang Jianjun. -Here.
جانغ جيان جون هنا
Liu Xuejun.
ليو شو جون
Liu Guoqi.
ليو قوه تشي
-Yes, here! -Here!
حاضر حاضر
-Yang Erhua. -Here.
‫يانغ أر هوا حاضر
-Zheng Sanchuang.
تشنغ سان اقتحم حاضر
Yao Binbin!
ياو بين بين
Xu Wenguo!
شو ون قوه